[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 5]
But whenever I look at them,
I feel
that the soul behind these paintings,
no matter how much time has passed,
or how many names they've taken,
seems to have been the same person all along.
Someone
I have loved with all my heart.
Autumn Moon in the Forest.
Autumn Moon in the Forest
is over here.
This is Autumn Moon in the Forest.
It has no artist's signature either,
nor any record of provenance.
Yet to me,
there's something strangely familiar about it.
As if it was always meant to belong here.
What a shame.
It's only here on temporary deposit.
It's not part of the museum's collection.
Qiu's feeling a little unwell.
I'll take her home first.
This is far enough.
Director Lin, please stay.
Miss Song,
are you all right?
We're sorry for dropping by unannounced today.
Thank you for your hospitality, Director Lin.
The pleasure was mine.
Perhaps the two of you and I are somehow meant to cross paths.
Miss Song seemed
particularly moved by those paintings today.
If you don't mind,
could we exchange contact information?
If you'd like to come back later,
feel free to stop by anytime.
Sorry,
she'd rather not.
Sure.
Thank you.
Ning Changyue, what's gotten into you?
Don't tell me you don't recognize him.
He's Lin Huai.
Look at the way he looks at you.
So what if he's Lin Huai?
He's been reincarnated.
He's crossed the Bridge of Forgetfulness
and drunk the Potion of Oblivion.
He's forgotten his past lives long ago.
He's just an ordinary modern man now,
a man who happens to collect paintings.
An ordinary man?
Would an ordinary man go out of his way to collect every painting
you've made over the past 3,000 years?
Are you lying to me,
or are you lying to yourself?
Where are you going?
I don't like people touching my car.
It's dirty.
I'm getting it washed.
Ning Changyue,
I don't know what kind of fit you're throwing,
but wasn't our common goal
to find the map of the pact
and put an end to our immortality?
You saw it yourself today.
Autumn Moon in the Forest is at the Autumn Art Gallery.
So we'll inevitably
have to deal with Director Lin more often.
If you don't like it,
I can go by myself.
And another thing,
we've been together
for more than 20 years,
but we're not really husband and wife anymore.
We both know that.
So you don't need to
put on this jealous act.
An act?
You're right. I don't need to put on an act.
♪ My heart aches as if it's tearing through my chest ♪
♪ Shattered into pieces ♪
♪ Until my lungs have nothing left ♪
What is wrong with you?
♪ My heart aches as if it's tearing through my chest ♪
♪ Shattered into pieces ♪
♪ Until my lungs have nothing left ♪
♪ I give up all that was beautiful, just to find release ♪
Song Yiqiu.
♪ Leave it all behind and run away with me ♪
If I really dropped the act,
could you handle it?
♪ Leaving all tenderness behind, escaping this torment ♪
Ning Changyue, what were you doing?
Why?
Why do your eyes look so familiar?
Morning.
-I was going to... -I'll first go...
-I was just... -I'm going to the bathroom.
-Actually, I... -Then I'll have breakfast.
Are you two all right?
-We're fine. -We're fine.
-I... -I...
We're fine.
What could possibly be wrong between us?
Exactly.
There's something.
I just remembered.
I have somewhere to be today.
I need to go now.
I... I'm just going to go...
You...
What time will you be back?
I don't know.
You're keeping regular hours.
They clearly have something going on.
You're right. I don't need to put on an act.
Where should I go?
To the art gallery.
Right.
I didn't get a chance to
really look at Autumn Moon in the Forest last time.
Wait.
It's Monday. The museum is closed.
[Hexin Psychological Clinic]
So you two slept together?
Of course not.
And besides,
I was talking about my friend.
Your friend.
So,
your friend kissed her ex-husband,
and that one kiss
kept her up all night?
And they still live under the same roof.
Now things are awkward,
and she doesn't know how to act around him?
Exactly.
Dr. Xie,
where's your professional ethics?
Right now,
it's my lunch break.
I'm talking to you
as Xie He.
I didn't charge you.
Besides,
after living with her ex-husband for so many years,
she kisses him once
and loses her head so badly she has to see a therapist?
That's adorable.
It's not like that.
They are not in that kind of relationship.
And they're living together now
because
there's...
There's a reason they have no choice.
Then why don't you get back together?
We could never be together again.
I mean my friend.
They stopped loving each other a long time ago.
My friend especially,
and her ex-husband even more.
They don't love each other anymore.
How could they not?
Dr. Xie?
I mean,
people are
creatures of desire.
Especially adults.
Desire can be a form of love, too.
But desire can also be about winning.
What if her ex-husband is just driven by the need to win?
Think about it.
Your friend kissed him
and still felt completely flustered.
That means she still has feelings for him.
Even if she won't admit it,
she can't fake feelings or desire.
You need to get your friend
to face her most primal desires.
Song Yiqiu,
you're avoiding me.
You two have a history that goes back lifetimes.
Even Lin Huai's reincarnation couldn't make him forget you.
You wouldn't happen to be going after him, would you?
Uncle.
Here's all the information on your rival.
How do I compare to him?
Am I really that far behind?
He's young, handsome, highly educated, and a rich heir.
His family situation is uncomplicated.
He sounds like the perfect boyfriend.
Aren't I?
Maybe for an ordinary person.
But for Ms. Song,
you're just an ex-husband who refuses to disappear.
The secret to love is novelty.
People always go for the new ones...
But,
Lin Huai has one fatal flaw,
and it's your only advantage.
Go on.
Lin Huai is just an ordinary man.
If Ms. Song really falls in love with him,
she'll have, at most, a few decades with him.
And after he dies,
you'll be the only one left by her side again.
Exactly.
That makes sense.
But
we ordinary people
know that life has an end,
so we love without holding anything back.
To grow old together and die together
with the person you love,
that's the most romantic thing
I can imagine.
You need to get your friend
to face her most primal desires.
[Ning Changyue]
Isn't it just about human desire?
Who could that possibly scare?
She can't fake feelings or desire.
♪ Whispers and judging eyes swirl around us ♪
You need to get your friend
to face her most primal desires.
♪ The dying embers consume the flames completely ♪
The most primal desires?
I've lived for 3,000 years.
What haven't I seen?
The most primal desires
call for the most primal solution.
Hello.
How many do you want?
-Miss. -Miss.
-Hello, miss! -Hello, miss!
Good evening, Miss.
Miss!
Come on, Miss.
Come on, bottoms up.
Have a drink.
Drink up.
A toast to you, Miss.
Come on, Miss.
Have some watermelon.
Here, have another piece.
Yu Tu,
is Qiu back yet?
No.
It's so late, and it's raining.
Where on earth did she go?
Where's Madam?
Tell her to come see me.
M-Master.
Madam, she...
You're worried about her?
Then go find her.
What happened to her?
Speak.
Madam, she...
ran away.
Then bring her back.
Madam said she never wants to see you again.
She's 3,000 years old.
She's not even afraid of death.
Why would I worry about her?
I'm going out for a walk.
Stubborn to the very end.
Why is it raining in the bathroom?
♪ Watch me die ♪
♪ Fall and rise ♪
♪ I am brave ♪
♪ You will find, find your way ♪
♪ No matter if you win or lose ♪